{
    "id": "a182e218715f4de2803b03c0469dfc27",
    "title": "Enough or Too | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The coat was ………………… so I didn’t buy it.",
            "description": "Too means 'more than is required'.",
            "answers": [
                "too expensive",
                "enough expensive",
                "expensive enough"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "354b435a0769414fa521290326e61f5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "If the water is ......................, we can go for a swim.",
            "description": "Enough goes after the adjective or adverb it modifies. ",
            "answers": [
                "too warm",
                "enough warm",
                "warm enough"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7b7480d646a84d7890b50864c0800357"
        },
        {
            "question": "His theories are …………………. to understand.",
            "description": "Too shows unwanted extremes. ",
            "answers": [
                "too difficult",
                "difficult enough",
                "enough difficult"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "26e82e3674f9434ab9240438c662f2d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "We didn’t manage to sell ………………….",
            "description": "When enough modifies a noun, it goes before the noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "tickets enough",
                "enough tickets"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a8051718a8c44799b0d069ad80b60c2d"
        },
        {
            "question": "There were ...................... people at the party.",
            "description": "Too cannot modify a noun however, it can go before words like many or much to indicate numbers or quantity. ",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too many"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5a31f041247447dcac38cd77df381e6c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ..................... to handle this job.",
            "description": "Enough goes after the adjective it modifies. ",
            "answers": [
                "experienced enough",
                "enough experienced",
                "too experienced"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "29e699f42be344fb810a620d760fee85"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………… to handle the situation.",
            "description": "Use 'too' to talk about unwanted or undesirable extremes. ",
            "answers": [
                "too immature",
                "immature enough",
                "enough immature"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "264fe3535afa4a36a809aa1baef5681e"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is never ……………….. to start.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "late enough",
                "enough late",
                "too late"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fef4e041ba17448fa36e83f46283e3b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………. to have a baby.",
            "description": "Both ‘too old’ and ‘old enough’ are possible here with different meanings. She is too old to have a baby. (= She cannot have a baby now because she is too old.) / She is old enough to have a baby. (= She is of the right age to have a baby.)",
            "answers": [
                "too old",
                "old enough",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e0f14b7facac4db88daa73f50c6878fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "I quit because I had had ..................... their quarreling.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough",
                "enough of",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2fdaf662ef64948b77d919621112115"
        }
    ]
}